<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 08:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Shadowrun 5e Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/shadowrun-5e-mega-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Become a Shadowrunner</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hide. Survive. Do what it takes, and you might even thrive inside the cracks in the world of <em>Shadowrun</em>—the legendary tabletop role-playing game that splices fantasy and cyberpunk sci-fi. This mega bundle features everything runners need to make a dangerous living on the streets and in the Matrix, including the <em>Core Rulebook (5E)</em>, guides to armed combat and street magic, and more sourcebooks exploring the dystopian Sixth World. Plus, your purchase helps support Global FoodBanking Network!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity by Packt 2023</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cybersecurity-packt-2023-books</link>
      <description>Tactics and strategy for cybersecurity</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn IT security essentials and stay vigilant in the ever-evolving cybersecurity space with this bundle from Packt! This library of dozens of ebooks will help prepare you for a career, equip you with practical techniques & tactics for real-world situations, and help you think like a hacker to safeguard your systems. Plus, your purchase helps support Save the Children!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goosebumps Collection by Scholastic Inc.</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/goosebumps-collection-scholastic-inc-books</link>
      <description>A terrifyingly fun treasury of R. L. Stine tales</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[For more than 30 years, R. L. Stine has been scaring and delighting young minds with his iconic <em>Goosebumps</em> series. Now, readers of all ages can discover the monsters, mysteries, and malevolent ventriloquist dummies that sparked the imaginations—and haunted the dreams—of generations in <em>The Ghost Next Door</em>, <em>Let's Get Invisible!</em>, <em>It Came from Beneath the Sink!</em>, and more. Get a treasury of over 30 ebooks, and help support Active Minds with your purchase! <br><br><a style="color:#EF9741"><em>This bundle is available to U.S. customers only.</em></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elfquest: The Complete Dark Horse Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/elfquest-complete-dark-horse-collection-books</link>
      <description>Journey to the World of Two Moons</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover the saga of Cutter, chief of the elfin tribe of the Wolfriders, and his epic quest across the World of Two Moons in <em>ElfQuest</em>, Wendy and Richard Pini’s long-running fantasy graphic novel series. This collection features every volume of the series published by Dark Horse, including <em>The Complete ElfQuest</em>, <em>The Final Quest</em>, and <em>Stargazer’s Hunt</em>. Celebrate 45 years of <em>ElfQuest</em>, and help support The Hero Initiative with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think Like a Programmer by No Starch</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/think-like-programmer-no-starch-books</link>
      <description>Blueprints for better coding</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Train your brain to think like a programmer with the trusted and entertaining experts of No Starch Press! Start to understand the machine mind in Randall Hyde’s three-part <em>Write Great Code</em> series.  Learn about system architecture, data structures, recursion, algorithmic thinking, and more. Teach yourself foundational principles that will help improve your skills with virtually any programming language, and help support the Electronic Frontier Foundation with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encore Fallout RPG &amp; 3D Miniatures by Modiphius</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/fallout-rpg-and-3d-miniatures-encore-modiphius-books</link>
      <description>Tabletop warfare and role-playing in the wasteland </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Journey into the Vaults, ruined cities, and radioactive wastes of <em>Fallout: Wasteland Warfare</em> with this bundle of tabletop combat & role-playing books and 3D print files from Modiphius! Prepare for life and death in the post-apocalypse with a digital pack full of rulebooks, RPG expansions, campaign handbooks, and more ebooks. Bring your adventures and battles to life with 3D printable (STL format) terrain and miniatures. Explore <em>Fallout</em> on your tabletop, and help support Trees, Water, People; or the charity of your choice.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Game Development by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/unreal-game-development-packt-encore-books</link>
      <description>Learn 3D game development with Unreal Engine 5</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Unreal Engine 5 is the industry-leading 3D game design software that the professionals use to create today’s top games. This carefully crafted bundle contains video courses and books that will guide you through building your first video game, creating incredible 3D environments, and a survival horror game. Start your journey towards getting paid to make video games today. <br><br>Your purchase of this bundle will help support Save the Children, working to provide life-saving assistance and long-term relief in response to the Türkiye and Syria earthquake.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2000 AD Character Spotlight by Rebellion</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/2000-ad-character-spotlight-rebellion-books</link>
      <description>Judge Dredd, Slaine, Nikolai Dante, and more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The Galaxy's Greatest Comics are back! The famed British science-fiction magazine <em>2000 AD</em> has been entertaining readers for years, and given the world some of comics’ most beloved and celebrated authors and artists. This thrilling bundle highlights some of </em>2000 AD</em>’s most iconic characters with books like <em>Judge Dredd Day of Chaos: Endgame</em>, <em>Slaine: The Horned God</em>, and <em>Nikolai Dante: Sympathy for the Devil</em>—among dozens of others. Explore some of Britain’s most popular comic book characters, and help support Cancer Research UK!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>