<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 18:45:06 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Unparalleled Puzzlers</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/unparalleled-puzzlers</link>
      <description>Melt your mind with these beloved brainbreakers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Think laterally, ponder perplexing perspectives, and challenge your brain in thrilling new ways with this bundle of unparalleled puzzle games! Change the world to change the rules of the award-winning <em>Baba Is You</em>. Piece together idyllic village landscapes in the relaxing <em>Dorfromantik</em>. Explore the enigmatic realms of <em>Creaks</em>, <em>The Last Campfire</em>, and more, and help support Razom for Ukraine with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steamy Sakura Special: 4 Complete Series and More</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/steam-sakura-special-bundle</link>
      <description>A steamy collection of visual novels &amp; more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in stories of the succubi, dark witches, and knights of Winged Cloud's <em>Sakura</em> franchise in this collection of adult-themed visual novels! This bundle features every entry released so far in the <em>Sakura Succubus</em>, <em>Sakura Knight</em>, <em>Sakura Forest Girls</em>, <em>Sakura MMO</em> series, along with a trio of other popular <em>Sakura</em> games, including the RPG <em>Sakura Dungeon</em>. Plus, your purchase helps support Direct Relief! <br/><br/><strong><a style="color: #ef9741;">Content in this bundle is intended for mature audiences.</a></strong>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fishing Season: Bassmaster &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/fishing-season-bassmaster-more</link>
      <description>The ultimate fishing game catch</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Live out your pro angler fantasy with this bundle of fishing games from the sim masters at Dovetail Games! Dive deep into the realism and competition of <em>Bassmaster Fishing</em>, plus a tackle box full of add-on content including new lakes, officially licensed equipment, and more. Chase monster marine life in <em>The Catch: Carp &amp; Coarse</em>, pursue a career in <em>Fishing Sim World: Pro Tour</em>, and more, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Black Creators and Characters</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/celebrating-black-creators-and-characters</link>
      <description>Play for a purpose during Black History Month</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[February is Black History Month, when people in the U.S. and around the world look back and reflect on the struggles and hard-won achievements of Black people throughout history. To help mark the month in our own way, we’ve put together a bundle of great games by Black creators along with games featuring Black lead characters—with proceeds helping support the next generation of game dev and tech talent on their own learning journeys. <br/><br/>When you pick up this bundle, you’ll experience gripping stories like the cinematic saga of Lincoln Clay in <b>Mafia III</b>, and stalk the underworld in the acclaimed remastered <b>Shadow Man</b>. You’ll support the work of Black devs through Interabang Entertainment’s <b>Jay &amp; Silent Bob: Mall Brawl</b>, Strange Scaffold’s <b>An Airport for Aliens Currently Run By Dogs</b>, and more. <br/><br/>Your purchase will also help support <b>Gameheads</b>, who envisions a world where low income youth and youth of color are equipped to thrive and succeed in any field they choose, including the tech and video game industries. <br/><br/><em>Learn more about how Humble is celebrating Black History Month on <a href="https://blog.humblebundle.com/2023/02/01/celebrating-black-history-month-with-great-games-and-causes/" style="color:#1695df">our blog</a>.</em>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>