<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://go-humble.github.io</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>shimst3r+rss@gmail.com (Nils Müller)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 08:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spanish Language and Travel by Lonely Planet and Utalk</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/spanish-language-and-travel-lonely-planet-and-utalk-software</link>
      <description>Your passport to learning &amp; adventure</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get ready to explore Spanish-speaking regions of the Americas and Europe with this bundle of Lonely Planet travel guides and uTalk, the easy-to-use language-learning app! Find out what to see, what to skip, and what hidden discoveries await in places like Mexico, Argentina, Columbia, and Spain. Learn to speak and understand Latin American Spanish, Basque, Galician, and more languages in practical, everyday situations. Plus, your purchase will support One Tree Planted. <br><br><em>Keep an eye out for more bundles featuring different Lonely Planet destinations &amp; uTalk languages throughout the year.</em>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eldamar Photo Graphics Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/eldamar-photo-graphics-software</link>
      <description>Transform your photos &amp; designs</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Enhance your images with this bundle of photo editing and digital artistry tools from Eldamar Studio! Take your photos to the next level with tens of thousands of cinematic overlays, professional LUTs, hi-res backgrounds, presets, and other versatile image-crafting tools. Plus, your purchase helps support Save the Children!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Python Programming MEGA Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-python-programming-mega-bundle-zenva-software</link>
      <description>Learn programming with Python</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get started with Python—the world's most popular programming language! Loved by pros and hobbyists alike, this easy-to-learn language is used for web development, game creation, AI, robotics, computer vision, automating tasks, and even space exploration! You'll learn by building real projects with Python, and work with Pygame, SQL, Tkinter, Kivy, and Pandas—all while supporting NPower with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluralsight Beginners Web Development</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/pluralsight-beginners-web-development-software</link>
      <description>Get started in the world of web development </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the fundamentals of modern web development and jump-start your career with this beginners’ bundle from Pluralsight! The 20 courses in this curriculum are designed to help you build a solid foundation in key concepts and essential skills, including HTML5, CSS, and JavaScript. Get into web development no matter your skill level, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total Performance, Protection and Privacy</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/total-performance-protection-and-privacy-software</link>
      <description>Your complete PC care collection</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Keep your machine running smoothly and safeguard your system with this bundle of essential PC software. Fix and speed up your PC automatically with the award-winning <em>System Mechanic</em>. Protect your PC from virus and malware with <em>System Shield</em>. Help secure yourself online with <em>Privacy Guardian</em>. Get an instant tool kit of useful utilities, and help support Direct Relief in their ongoing humanitarian response efforts for the people of Türkiye and Syria impacted by the recent tragic earthquakes.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synty&#39;s POLYGON Game Dev Assets Bundle 3</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/syntys-polygon-game-dev-assets-bundle-3-software</link>
      <description>Build your 3D game with these stylish, versatile assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add some low-poly, high-style 3D characters, environments, and props to your game with our latest POLYGON bundle from Synty! This flexible and eclectic library of over 5000 assets will help you develop games for a variety of genres in Unity and Unreal. Create treacherous dungeons, Wild West worlds, and wartorn battlefields. Prototype natural forests and bustling cities, and help support charity with your purchase! <br><br>Your purchase of this bundle will help support Direct Relief in their ongoing humanitarian response efforts for the people of Türkiye and Syria impacted by the recent tragic earthquakes.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything you need to know about CAD</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/everything-you-need-to-know-about-cad-software</link>
      <description>Your complete CAD software &amp; learning bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Want to create using CAD (Computer-Aided Design)? Pick up this bundle of 2D and 3D CAD software—plus a library of learning resources—and get started right away. This comprehensive bundle features: </p> <ul> <li>Advanced CAD software for a variety of design needs, including the 3D Pro, 3D, and 2D editions of <em>BeckerCAD 14</em>.</li> <li>Training guide ebooks for a range of popular CAD tools—including AutoCAD, Revit, 3DS Max, and more.</li> </ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Assets</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-military-game-assets-software</link>
      <description>Tanks &amp; more military game assets for Unreal Engine</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get a massive supply drop of military-themed game assets with this bundle curated for Unreal Engine developers! Featuring ready-to-roll tank blueprints, meshes and models for supplies, fully realized environments, and much more, this bundle will equip you with the assets you need to create FPSes and battlefield sims. Plus, your purchase will support Direct Relief!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Creative Coding UI / UX Online Course</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-creative-coding-ui-ux-online-course-software</link>
      <description>Learn to build awesome user experiences</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Want to make intuitive and elegant interactive experiences? Learn to design, code, and create with this bundle of UX and UI courses from Mammoth Interactive! You’ll explore principles and best practices behind great websites and mobile apps, and learn the tools you need to bring your own to life—including Figma, Python, React, Xcode, Google Material Design, and more. Plus, your purchase will support NPower!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>